[Waco] Memorial Baptist Church records, Inclusive: 1943-2003, undated, Bulk: 1943-2003
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Financial, 1953-2002; 3
  - Reports (3 of 3), 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Pastor’s Expenses, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Budgets (1 of 2), 1960-2002 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Budgets (2 of 2), 1960-2002 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Annual Report and Financial Report, 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Ledger, 1967-1973 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Ledger, 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Ledger, 1977-1980 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Ledger, 1986-1989 (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Book Noting Disbursement, 1954-1962 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Ledger, 1976-1991 (Box 9 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Ledger, 1981-1986 (Box 16, Folder Item 2)
- Literary Productions, 1943-2002; 4
  This series contains the literary productions of the Waco Memorial Baptist Church. Such literary productions include a history of the church, Waco Baptist Association letters and reports, invitations, church certificates, membership records, membership cards and church bulletins. The materials are in good condition.
  - Homecoming Materials, 1973, 1988, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Homecoming Mailing List, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 45th Anniversary, 1988 May 15 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 50th Anniversary, Kenneth L. Dill Pastor, 1933 May 16 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Anniversary (Homecoming), 1998 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Job Descriptions and Procedures, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - History (1 of 4), 1943-2002 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - History (2 of 4), 1943-2002 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - History (3 of 4), 1943-2002 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - History (4 of 4), 1943-2002 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Waco Baptist Association Reports (1 of 3), 1974-1992 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Waco Baptist Association Reports (2 of 3), 1974-1992 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Waco Baptist Association Reports (3 of 3), 1974-1992 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Church Profile (1 of 3), 1990-2002 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Church Profile (2 of 3), 1990-2002 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Church Profile (3 of 3), 1990-2002 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Certificates, 1943-2002 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Membership: 2002 December 21 and Dropped from Rolls (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Church Bulletins (1 of 2), 1981-1986 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Church Bulletins (2 of 2), 1981-1986 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Church Bulletins (1 of 14), 1992-2002 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Church Bulletins (2 of 14), 1992-2002 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Church Bulletins (3 of 14), 1992-2002 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Church Bulletins (4 of 14), 1992-2002 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Church Bulletins (5 of 14), 1992-2002 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Church Bulletins (6 of 14), 1992-2002 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Church Bulletins (7 of 14), 1992-2002 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Church Bulletins (8 of 14), 1992-2002 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Church Bulletins (9 of 14), 1992-2002 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Church Bulletins (10 of 14), 1992-2002 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Church Bulletins (11 of 14), 1992-2002 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Church Bulletins (12 of 14), 1992-2002 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Church Bulletins (13 of 14), 1992-2002 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Church Bulletins (14 of 14), 1992-2002 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Church Bulletins (1 of 11), 1995-1998 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Church Bulletins (2 of 11), 1995-1998 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Church Bulletins (3 of 11), 1995-1998 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Church Bulletins (4 of 11), 1995-1998 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Church Bulletins (5 of 11), 1995-1998 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Church Bulletins (6 of 11), 1995-1998 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Church Bulletins (7 of 11), 1995-1998 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Church Bulletins (8 of 11), 1995-1998 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Church Bulletins (9 of 11), 1995-1998 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Church Bulletins (10 of 11), 1995-1998 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Church Bulletins (11 of 11), 1995-1998 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - General, 1973-2002 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Guest Book (1 of 2), 1983-2002 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Guest Book (2 of 2), 1983-2002 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Membership Cards (1 of 3), 1943-1989 (Box 11 OVZ)
  - Membership Cards (2 of 3), 1943-1989 (Box 12 OVZ)
  - Membership Cards (3 of 3), 1943-1989 (Box 13 OVZ)
- Scrapbooks, 1954-1964; 5
  This series contains the scrapbook from the Memorial Baptist Church Youth Council group. It includes photographs of members and parties, bulletins, invitations and other short publications concerning the Youth Council. The materials are in good condition.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  Photographic print
  - Memorial Baptist Church Youth Council, Loose Materials (1 of 4), 1962-1964 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Memorial Baptist Church Youth Council, Loose Materials (2 of 4), 1962-1964 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Memorial Baptist Church Youth Council, Loose Materials (3 of 4), 1962-1964 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Memorial Baptist Church Youth Council, Loose Materials (4 of 4), 1962-1964 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Memorial Baptist Church Youth Council, 1962-1964 (Box 10 OVZ, Folder 2)
- Photographs, 1943-1973; 6
  This series contains photographs pertaining to the internal church organization, the Youth Council, photographs of the church buildings and meeting places, and photographs from various church events. The material is in good condition.
  - General (1 of 2), 1943-1995 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - General (2 of 2), 1943-1995 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Church (1 of 6), 1973, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Church (2 of 6), 1973, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Church (3 of 6), 1973, undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Church (4 of 6), 1973, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Church (5 of 6), 1973, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Church (6 of 6), 1973, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)